Bonjour!
I went to Paris, France with a boo-boo and yes, what a trip!
I've been to Paris, France!
I'm in Boo-Boo, and I'd like to go there for the first time, so I'd like to say hello to you.
I'm Rika Ueda, black belt, white belt, mc, and I'm Hina Haru, a big fashionable supporter with a bar tension
Yes mail lion prince yana like it Yes absorption food culture lovers association president person is pla
Yes I deliver pink yell to the blue earth Yes I am Natsuya leader blue leader
Yes, I'm Kyamai, the leader of the dance before 3 to visit the sweet potato.
3 and then we are
I want to be pattychal!
me
We are also going to perform at japan expo paris, and in between, we are going to be on location in paris for 2 days!
I was on location in Paris for two days!
me me japan
Today, we're going to visit sightseeing spots in Paris, and on the second day, we're going to shoot a big scene in the downtown area of Needles.
Ai-chan, how do you like the image of needles?
I knew it! I knew it! I knew it!
I see.
I want to say "reacher".
I'm sure there's something in there.
Why did you come here?
For your future idols.
Boo-boo, here in Paris, for the first time, your eyes are not moving anymore... delicious!
Please bring back various regions to Japan, so I have a quiz for you
Yes, yes, yes, yes...
I think I see you in a little bit.
I'd like to give you a quiz.
This is a monument to a great Frenchman who, at the age of 13, received a revelation from God and won the French army out of the 100 Years War.
He is said to have had an epiphany at the age of 13 that led the French army to victory in the 100 Years War.
I think he's a Frenchman from Reims, but I don't know why he's 13.
I'm sure you've all heard of him.
I've heard so much about you.
It's not Lupin Lupin.
I may have lived to see Buber... go in at the end.
Let's go!
I'm sure you're right...
I'm sure you've never done it before... not even at school... but while doing it... while doing it...
I'm sure you'll understand if I ask you what the letters are at first.
Hold on.
Hold on! Hold on!
Maybe it's a lot of letters.
I'm sure you'll understand if I say so.
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Oh my goodness!
La Préon, Jeanne d'Or.
Love, Jeanne, if only...
Wah!
Yes!
Nooooo!
She's singing!
I'm singing "The Idol World's..." right now.
I want to pray...
That's great!
Yes, I mean...
The Goddess of Liberty who leads her people
Also known as the goddess of freedom
with Ms. Jeanne Dorre-kun
Let's take a picture because it's accurate!
Oh!
Yes, then, we'll discover many things in this unknown land
I'd like to let you go to the idol castle!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go!
Wrong!
This is the place where we just shot the opening sequence.
It's called Bir Akem Bridge.
As you can see
It's the best place to see the whole view of the Eiffel Tower
It's the best place to see the whole view of the Eiffel Tower.
And below it, you know...
The Seine River, a UNESCO World Heritage Site.
The Seine River
You've heard of it, right?
I've heard of it.
I've heard so much about it
It's not so easy to see.
There are fish.
And you can fish, too.
I can fish too?
Yes.
I've heard of sea bass.
Sea bass.
Sea bass is called European perch.
You can catch it here, too.
It's called European Perch.
And they also have a huge catfish
I think I see a two-meter catfish.
Catfish?
Yes.
I don't see any.
No, I don't.
I haven't been able to imagine anything.
There are boats.
I think there are probably a lot of people who fish.
People who fish in Paris...
Sometimes they use cheese as bait.
Cheese?
Fishing.
That's fine.
It's fashionable.
I'd rather eat cheese than fish.
Sure, maybe a sourdough.
That's right.
Fish raised on cheese tastes so good!
Yes, it's like a condensation of flavors.
About fish food
Lilo, may I ask what your favorite sushi item is?
Any number of them!
I like tuna, salmon and bonito!
Bonito! That's amazing! Unexpected! Nice!
Delicious with ponzu!
How about you, Ai?
I like shrimp!
By the way, let's hear about soccer too!
I like inari, egg and leaf rolls, and seared cheese pork ribs!
Sushi! I don't care about fish!
I prefer shellfish.
I like scallops and red clams.
I see!
I definitely eat shrimp first shot.
But I live for the first shot.
Boiled?
Well, I don't know...
I eat them boiled, basically.
I don't know if they feed me raw, so...
I don't know. I'm waiting for everything.
Waiting?
I'm waiting.
Mie, you eat sushi?
Sushi?
What's your favorite dish?
I used to like salmon.
But lately I like white fish, like squid and Thai.
Aren't you an adult?
Suddenly I'm a high schooler.
Why are we talking about sushi in France?
You know what?
This is France.
It's because we're in France.
Japanese sushi!
Don't forget
Sushi with a French touch!
Sushi and macarons?
I want sushi.
Sushi, no!
Sushi?
I wonder if Mie is forbidden to eat in Paris.
I don't know.
Not now!
I want to be a cat in France!
Great!
Is there such a thing as a cat?
I haven't seen one yet.
Well, I'm going to go look for it.
I don't know... it could be on a boat or something.
I'm taking you with me.
There's a chance I can take you.
Let's go look for the cat, too.
Let's go.
Sushi Trip.
Sushi Trip
Good morning
Your future will do that kind of life
Here you go
Welcome home
Welcome home.
All French.
Can I talk to you?
Yes.
I'm new here.
Is this it?
Oh, here it is!
- I'm scared! I'm scared! Fear! Fear! Scary!
When we go to play, particitous!
One that can't sing for us
Yes, thank you. Interesting.
Yes, thank you, very funny.
Yes, thank you, very interesting.
Yes, thank you, very interesting
Yes, hi, interesting
Yes, hi, interesting.
Yes, thank you, very interesting.